Neha Sharma

Web Designer

- Nehasharma38140@gmail.com
- **** 9719922147
- ₱ H.No-602 B-10 Navkar Apartment flat no-14 ward no3 Mehrauli near kali mandir road, New delhi, 110030, Delhi, India
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/neha-sharma-274006191



SUMMARY

I am a Web Designer with a MCA degree from IGNOU University. I have 2 years of experience in Web designing with XLNC Team in Gurgaon. I have designed 20+ websites in wordpress and logos, banners, layout designing in graphic adobe photoshop and illustration. I am also learning Web Design and Graphic Design on LearnVern.

EXPERIENCE

11/2019 - 07/2021 Web Designer

XLNC Team

Job Description

I have 2 years of experience in graphic designing with XLNC Team in Gurgaon. I have designed 20+ websites in WordPress and logos, banners, layout designing in graphic adobe photoshop and illustration, html, CSS designing. last working project is www.probomedlabs.com

03/2019 - 06/2021 Programme Assistant

Restless Development India

Job Description

Worked in Scratch Program designed by IBM to educate girls. I had worked there as a Scratch Programmer to teach students of 5 govt schools and maintain the report sheet. Scratch software module1 and module2

09/2019 - 11/2019 Web Designer

Fourtek India Pvt. Ltd.

Job Description

I was working as a Intern current clients project either UI design and graphic design

EDUCATION

08/2015 - 09/2019	MCA IGNOU University	60%
06/2012 - 06/2015	B.C.A IGNOU University	62%
07/2011 - 07/2012	12th Pass C.B.S.E	56%
07/2010 - 07/2011	10th Pass C.B.S.E	52%

COURSES

HTML and HTML5 Course

LearnVern

CSS3 Course

LearnVern

wordpress

learnvern

HOBBIES

listen music

travelling at hill station

LANGUAGE

English

hindi

KEY SKILLS

 HTML

CSS

Javascript

Photoshop

Illustrator

Wordpress

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Website Designing graphic design